在初始呼叫之后，甚至在初始呼叫期间，
After the initial call or even during
the initial call, towards the end,
或者可能是另外一个电话你可能会有一系列的问题
or maybe it might be a separate call, you
might get a series of prescreen questions.
通常这些都是大公司想在你之前对你进行审查
Usually these are the larger companies
that wanna kind of vet you out before you
开始，因为面试一个人拿资源，需要人力。
get started, because interviewing someone
takes resources, it takes manpower.
人们需要花时间去做这些事情。
It takes people that have to take time
out of their day to do these things.
所以他们想让你的问题
So they wanna give prescreen questions,
say,
这个人起码有一点资格做前期工程师吗 ?
is this person at least a little bit
qualified to be a front-end engineer?
因此，我将这些基本行问题视为 JavaScript 知识。
So I consider these base line
questions for JavaScript knowledge.
那就把他们开除吧
So let's fire them off.
const， let 和 var 之间有什么区别 ?
What is the difference between const,
let, and var?
有人吗
Anybody?
>> 作用域。
&gt;&gt; Scope.
>> 更多。
&gt;&gt; More.
> > 更多信息 ? > > 嗯，
&gt;&gt; More on that?
&gt;&gt; Yeah,
是的 [ LAUGH] >> Var 一般是全局的。
yeah [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Var is global, generally.
让我们再缩小一点，并确定常量。
Let is a little bit more narrow,
and const is fixed.
如果您稍后尝试更改该规则，那么您将由某些 JS 借出规则来进行修改。
You'll get yelled at by some JS lent
rule if you try to change it later.
> > 好的，没问题。
&gt;&gt; Okay, that was okay.
>> 好 >> 好吧。
&gt;&gt; Okay
&gt;&gt; So have that each other.
没事的没事的
It was okay.
范围是找到它的好方法。
Scope is a good way to finding it.
Var，我不认为是全球性的，无论是在全球范围内，还是在全球范围内
Var, I wouldn't say is global,
its global to whatever scope it but
外面不会有泄漏的
it's not gonns leak outside.
但我们的人说这是不可改变的但是人们说这是不可改变的
But yes, const, it's not immutable,
people say it's immutable, but
我们对 immutable 可能有不同的定义
we probably have different
definitions of immutable.
你不能把一个常量指向另一个指针。
You can't point a const
to a different pointer.
但您可以修改该对象，也可以添加对象，或者
But you can modify that,
you can add objects, or
您可以向对象添加属性，从数组中添加内容。
you can add properties to an object,
things from array.
我们不能改变这个指针
We can't change that pointer.
您可以更改指针，但是
Let, you can change the pointer, but
只有在封闭的范围内才能确定
it's only gonna be scoped
to whatever the closure is.
将 var 提升到顶部。
And var is hoisted to the top.
所以我们想
So const and let,
如果你先去找他们再给他们一个参考
if you try to access them before
they're gonna throw a reference there,
var 将会抛出未定义的值。
var will just throw undefined.
很简单
Pretty simple.
这不是骗你的问题
These aren't trick questions.
你能在多快的时间里回答这些问题
It's just how fast and how comfortably
do you answer these questions?
好吧，有错误的答案，但是没有那么多错误的答案。
Okay, there are wrong answers, but there
aren't as many wrong answers to this.
就像，这个人对自己的 JavaScript 知识有信心吗 ?
It's just like, does this person feel
confident in their JavaScript knowledge?
这不是骗术不是骗术
That's it, not a trick.
作为采访者，你不是在耍他们。
And as the interviewer,
you're not trying to trick them.
这不是骗你的问题
These aren't trick questions.
这不像特里维亚的问题
These aren't like one of trivia questions.
这些都是你知道你在说什么吗
These are just like,
do you know what you're talking about?
有人向我解释典型的遗产吗
Someone explain prototypical
inheritance to me?
谁谁都有
Anybody, anybody at all.
> > 我就这样做了。
&gt;&gt; I just did.
> > [LAUGH] 好，什么是原型?
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] All right, what's a prototype?
没有人这是很有趣的工程
Nobody, this is funny engineering.
好吧没人
All right, nobody.
好的好的
Yeah, take a shot.
我要开枪了
&gt;&gt; I'll take a shot.
因此，当对象继承自另一个对象时，
So when an object inherits
from another object,
如果它继承的对象具有某些功能或
if that object that it inherited
from has some functions or
属性，此新对象将具有这些属性。
properties, this new object,
it will have those.
> > 嗯我来吧
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I'll take that.
又不是诡计
Again, not a trick,
JavaScript 具有原型，对象的基线原型。
JavaScript has a prototype,
a baseline prototype of the object.
所有东西都是从物体上继承的，所以你可以做各种各样的事情。
Everything inherits from the object,
so you can do all sorts of things.
JavaScript 中的所有内容都有一个原型，
Everything in JavaScript has a prototype,
它具有继承自的基线对象。
it has a baseline object
that it inherits from.
当您基于其他对象创建新对象时，
And when you create a new object
based on the other object,
您可以继承所有这些属性，缺省情况下，
you can either inherit all those
properties, which you will be default, or
你可以用你自己的方式，以此类推。
you can overwrite them with your own and
so on, and so forth.
我通常用的，不是最好的。
The analogy I usually use,
it's not the best one.
这很不错是有孩子的父母
It's pretty good,
is parents with children.
你有一个棕色眼睛的父母，还有另一个有棕色眼睛的父母。
Do you have one parent with brown eyes,
you have another parent with brown eyes.
孩子可以有棕色眼睛
The child could have brown eyes, or
它可以写和有蓝色的眼睛之类的
it could over write it and
have blue eyes, something like that.
再一次我不是在找太多细节和深度
Again, I'm not looking for
too much detail or depth,
只是，你知道 JavaScript 中的原型是什么吗 ?
it's just, do you know what
prototype is in JavaScript?
因为它是我们所做的一切
Because it's underneath everything we do,
and
我希望你能了解到这一点
I expect you to have some
baseline knowledge about that.
它不一定要深入，但是不要在它 [ LAUGH]上发抖。
It doesn't have to be in depth,
but don't fumble on it [LAUGH].
别瞎猜
Don't guess.
如果你猜的话那就不难看出来了
If you're guessing,
that's pretty easy to tell.
如果是招聘者之类的问题的话
And a lot of times with these questions,
if it's a recruiter or things like that,
他们不一定是在 UI 工程中非常熟悉的
they're not necessarily super well
versed in UI engineering, they might be,
你永远不知道
you never know.
但他们会有一个普通的答案他们在寻找
But they're gonna have kind of a general
answer, and they're looking for
在那个范围内发生的事情
something that falls in that range.
同样，这不是一个真实的错误，也不是错误的或错误的。
Again, it's not a true or
false or right or wrong.
只是说这在 JavaScript中是什么意思 ?
It's just talking about what
does this mean in JavaScript?
>> 它是您在其中可以更改的当前作用域
&gt;&gt; It's the current scope
you're in which can change and
如果没有范围，即全局窗口，通常是对象吗 ?
if there is no scope,
that is the global window, object usually?
> > 完美回答正确
&gt;&gt; Perfect answer, exactly right.
我考虑了可以访问的所有内容的全局上下文。
I considered the global context of
everything that is available to access.
所以所有的物体和
So all the objects and
这些功能可供您使用，但未在本地定义。
functions are available to you
that are not locally defined.
是啊如果你还没想过这种事
Yeah, and
if you haven't thought about this kind of
高级的抽象问题好的
high level abstract questions,
yeah, that's okay.
这当然是为了这个
That's what this course is for.
DOM 的数据结构是什么 ?
What's the data structure of the DOM?
>> 树。
&gt;&gt; Tree.
> > 是，是树，就这样。
&gt;&gt; Yes, it's a tree, that's it.
[ LAUGH] 再次，不是一个诡计问题，你之前是否考虑过这个问题 ?
[LAUGH] Again, not a trick question,
just have you thought about this before?
什么是堆栈?
What is a stack?
是一个数据结构，对，对。
It's a data structure, right, yeah.
>> LIFO， FIFO。
&gt;&gt; LIFO, FIFO.
最后一个是先出去还是先出去
Last in, first out versus first in,
first out.
>> 哪一个 ?
&gt;&gt; Which one is which?
>> Stack 为 LIFO，提示为 FIFO >> Yes， LIFO， FIFO， Last in，
&gt;&gt; Stack is LIFO, cue is FIFO
&gt;&gt; Yes, LIFO, FIFO, Last in,
首先是堆栈，首先是第一组，作为提示。
First Out is the stack,
First in, First Out as a cue.
想想你是否需要一个心理模型
Think about if you need a mental model.
你是站着的那是提示
You're standing in line, that's a cue.
第一个到达那里的第一个人如果这是一个公平的路线
The first person that gets there's first
one that leaves if it's a fair line
堆栈是反向的
Stack is, it's reversed.
就像你的线，然后实际上是后面的人。
It's like you get line and then actually
it's people in the back that go first.
你就像什么 sammed ?
You're like, what, scammed again?
我讨厌去 [ INAUDIBLE ] 。
I hate going to [INAUDIBLE].
如何在 JavaScript 中创建这些结构 ?
How you create these
structures in JavaScript?
>> 批量和灌木，为堆栈工作。
&gt;&gt; Bulk and bush with work for Stack.
> > 是，是一个数组弹出和推移位。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, it is an array pop and
push shift.
是啊，你怎么能看出来图片元素是装在页面上的 ?
Yeah, how can you tell if an image
element is loaded on the page?
这个是更微妙的
This one is a little more nuanced but
有一个图片的加载元素你可以说它是在装的吗
there's an onload element of Images You
can just say is it on, has it loaded?
这回电话会被开除的
It'll fire that call back.
好，什么叫 ( ) 和申请()?
All right, what are call() and apply()?
>> 这是一种调用另一种方法的方法，但是
&gt;&gt; It's a way to call another method, but
如果你要改变你的范围的话通常会用它
usually use it if you have to change
the scope you're calling with.
我记不起来了是哪个 [ INAUDIBLE]
I can't remember which is
which [INAUDIBLE] I put.
> > 我也不可以。
&gt;&gt; I never can either.
没关系我是说
That's okay.
我想知道的是他们改变范围的方法
All I would wanna know on this question
is their ways of changing the scope
调用函数。
of the calling function.
对，调用是一系列自变量，并应用自变量数组。
Yeah, and call is a series of arguments
and applies an array of arguments.
不错我们不需要再申请了
Nice, we don't necessarily
need to apply as much anymore,
因为我们有道具，或者我们有数组传播，就像这样。
because we have props or
we have array spreading, things like that.
但我很想知道
But it'd be good to know.
什么是事件验证?
What is event validation?
传统上，如果您使用 HTML中的事件处理程序，
So traditionally,
if you have event handlers in HTML,
您可以将事件处理程序应用于要拥有的每个元素。
you could apply an event handler to
every single element you wanna have.
或者使用事件授权，您可以说我想拥有一个事件侦听器，并且
Or using event delegation, you could say
I wanna have one event listener, and
就在上面
that's at the top.
当你点击一些东西的时候
And when you click on something,
它只会泡到负责处理事件的家长
it just bubbles up to the parent
that handles the event.
这是一个活动代表团。
That's an event delegation.
我想找人知道这个 czz 事件的听众真的很贵
I would want someone to know this cuz
event listeners are really expensive on
每次渲染的时候都有一个页面会发生什么事吗
a page cuz every time it renders,
gotta be like did something happen?
发生什么事了吗
Did something happen?
因此，出于性能原因，最好有一个事件处理程序与 60 个事件处理程序。
So it's better to have one event handler
versus 60 for performance reasons.
事件授权。
Event delegation.
如果你说了些关于冒泡的东西，那也很好用。
If you said something about bubbling,
that's also good to use.
什么是工人?
What is a worker?
工作程序是您将在浏览器中使用以进行计算的工作
A worker is something you would use in
a browser to offload computationally
昂贵的工作
expensive work.
三种不同的线程 cubz JavaScript 是单线程的，如果您有
Three different thread cuz JavaScript is
single threaded, if you have something
就像数到一万，数字，你想做的事情，
that's like tactically prime to 10,000,
numbers, something you want to do that and
您没有阻止 UI， cuz 在 JavaScript中只有一个线程。
workers you're not blocking the UI,
cuz there's only one thread in JavaScript.
而这也是你使用的时候。
And that's when you use one as well.
好的谢谢你的提问
All right, those appreciate questions.
这些都是我被问到的问题你可能会问
These are questions that I've been asked,
that you may get asked and
我可以考虑好的关于 JavaScript的基本知识
that I can consider good
baseline knowledge of JavaScript.
我知道 HTML 的比较难因为我们不觉得
I know the HTML ones are a little tougher
because we don't actually think in
那样的话就可以有点小点了
that way, so those can be a little dicey.
但总的来说我希望每个人都能从球棒上知道这些问题
But in general, I would expect everyone
to know these questions off the bat,
就像把它们放了一样
just kind of pop them off.
再次，不寻求准确的正确答案。
Again, not looking for
precise correct answers.
我只想让他们知道他们在说什么
I just want that they have some
knowledge of what they're talking about.
但重要的是，我不问的原因是我没有问部落问题。
But importantly, why I didn't ask
is I didn't ask trivia questions.
我没问过什么对象加数组等于什么
I didn't ask what object
plus array equals,
我在采访中被问到了
which I've been asked in an interview.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why.
什么都没告诉我
That doesn't tell me anything.
它告诉我他们有一些奇怪的有趣知识
It tells me they have some
weird funny knowledge.
但你知道有趣的是你通过提问和
But you know what's funny is,
you get trivia questions and
我读了一个关于 JavaScript的奇怪的诡计
someone be like,
I read this weird trick about JavaScript.
我们会黑进新闻
We'll hack the news.
我要向某人问好
I'm gonna ask that to somebody.
这是否与工作有关 ?
Is that relevant to the job?
如果他们知道这事告诉你
If they know that,
does that inform you of anything that
他们除了知道一些部落问题外，还能做些什么呢 ?
they can do other than they
know some trivia questions?
所以如果你是采访者，不要问部落问题。
So if you're the interviewer,
don't ask trivia questions.
问你知道的问题
Ask questions that you know.
我明白我要面对的是更亲密的更亲密的关系
I see what I'm gonna face, its's even
real close, real closer, closer.
你可能觉得你的面试很简单
You're probably thinking
your interview is easy,
但这是因为你已经知道答案了
but that's because you already know
the answers to them, that's it.
那是我的大灰鼠
That's my big rat.
每个人都说我的面试我的问题很简单
Everybody says my interview,
my questions are easy.
我的基督教问题很简单我的采访很简单
My Christian questions are easy,
my interviews easy.
那是因为你已经知道答案了
That's cause you already know the answer.
如果你不知道答案
If you didn't know the answer,
你能不能解决你自己的面试问题
would you be able to solve
your own interview questions?
也许不是，如果我们是诚实的话，也许不是。
Probably not, if we're being honest,
probably not.
如果我是诚实的
If I'm being honest,
我已经问了问题，我甚至都不知道答案是什么。
I've asked questions that I wouldn't even
know the answer to right off the bat.
如果是的话，那是有效的面试问题吗 ?
If so, is that a valid interview question?
这是我真正想让我们严肃对待的行业。
This is something I really want us
to take seriously as an industry.
别再问问题了
Don't ask trivia questions.
别问奇怪的算法问题
Don't ask weird algorithm
questions that aren't relevant.
询问您是否知道答案或
Ask questions that you
would know the answer to or
在你的日常工作中是必需的
is necessary in your day to day working.
这也不是什么问题，对吧 ?
That's not much to ask, right?
这是应用程序，初始调用。
That was the application,
the initial call.
那真是太好了
That was a lot.
这已经是很多信息了。
That was a lot of information already.
CATSA 过程面试是一个磨磨人，它是关于耐力的，它是关于耐力的。
CATSA process interviewing is a grind,
it's about stamina, it's about endurance.
作为采访者，
And as the interviewer,
我想做的就是让那个过程尽量简单
what I wanna do is I wanna make
that process as easy as possible.
采访也不容易变好变好了
Interviews are not gonna be easy,
rhey're never gonna be easy.
他们不应该那么容易。
They shouldn't be easy.
我们赚了很多钱
We get paid a lot of money for
啊，但是最后我不喜欢擦伤，血汗。
we do, but at the end of the day I'm
not like bruised or bloody and sweaty.
也许我的背在我的电脑上，吃得太多免费的食物。
Maybe my back hurts from eating too much
free food as I'm leaning over my computer.
但最终我们赚了很多钱来做我们做的事
But at the end of the day we get paid
a lot of money to do what we do,
采访应该不容易，应该实现。
interviews should not be easy,
they should be fulfilling.
采访应该是第一次约会很尴尬有点挑战性
Interviews should be like a first date,
pretty awkward, a little challenging,
你得把你最好的脸放在前面
you have to put your best face forward.
最终，你觉得如果它能有效的话，你是对的，真的很令人满意。
At the end, do you think if it works out,
you're yeah, that was really satisfying.
我想我们应该认识彼此
I think we got to know each other.
我想我想和这个人一起继续这个旅程
I think I wanna continue on
this journey with this person.
你在这第二次约会
There you go on a second date.
对我的采访应该是这样的。
That to me is what a interview should be.
应该是在挑战和奖励，但是
It should be challenging and
rewarding at the same time, but
这不应该是令人沮丧的
it shouldn't be frustrating.
不太会问对吧
Not too much to ask, right?